OFIR ADATO

QA TESTER

@ ofiradatowork@gmail.com

J 050-9464923

Holon, Israel

in Ofir Adato

OfirAdato

ABOUT ME

Quality assurance and automation tester, understands and loves the world of testing, Theoretical as well as practical, including writing STP, STD, STR test documents. Practical experience in the testing processes including test management in Test Rail, Jira, Visual Studio bug reports and STR release. Understanding and experience working with CSS, HTML, java and selenium. Understanding of work processes (Agile, water fall).

WORK EXPERIENCE

QA TESTER

'CALL-FLOW'

▼ Tel-Aviv

Quality assurance in the customization department.

LEVEL B TECHNICIAN

'ONE-TALDOR'

April 2021 – January 2023

Petah Tiqwa

- · A level B technician of ATM machine.
- Technician of computer hardware.

FIELD SERVICE TECHNICIAN

'BRINKS'

Dec 2019 - April 2021

■ Tel-Aviv

• Technician of ATM machine.

MILITARY SERVICE

Signal Corps

march 2017 -nov 2019

Commanders course

- **2018**
- I served as a company sergeant and managed everything related to work arrangements, company tasks.
- Operation of faults in CISCO and JUNIPER routers and switches.

PROJECTS

Project 1

https://ofiradato.github.io/Ofir-website/

• My profile website

CERTIFICATIONS

Quality assurance - Tester "QA MASTERS"

June 2022 -October 2022

Automation - Tester
"QA MASTERS"

October 2022 - February 2023

SKILLS

SQL HTML CSS JAVA

Selenium | TestNG | PageFactory

SOFT SKILLS

Team Work Problem-Solving Responsibility

Self-Learning Strategic Thinking Flexibility

Hard-working Eye for detail

Motivator & Leader

LANGUAGES

EDUCATION

"OA MASTERS"

I JUNE 2022 - OCTOBER 2022

Thesis title: QA TESTER

"QA MASTERS"

Cotober 2022 - February 2023

Thesis title: AUTOMATION TESTER